SUTANTO

STUDENT



Profile

My name is Sutanto, and I am a 6th-semester student at Esa Unggul University majoring in Information Technology. I have experience running an online business at ReapStore for one year. I am proficient in using Adobe Photoshop and Microsoft Office. I am currently seeking a part-time job, freelance opportunity, or internship to further develop my skills and gain new experiences.

Education

2021 - Present

Esa Unggul University

2018 - 2021

Saint Joseph High School Social Major

Phone:

+62 813 1208 6533

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/sutanto19

Website:

sutanto19.github.io/Portofolio/

Email Adress:

Sutantow19@gmail.com

Address:

Pondok Ungu Permai Blok AL 14/1, Bekasi

Job Experience

2020-2021 Owner Online Shop Reap Store

- Take a photos and upload products to e-commerce.
- Reply to messages from customers.

2023-2023 Unity 2D Games

- Create a simple 2D based game system.
- Designed and implemented gameplay, control systems, and game logic.

2024-2024 Front End Website

- Built a responsive portfolio website.
- Created a YouTube clone using APIs.
- Developed a responsive food ordering website with authentication.

Skills

Photoshop Digital Marketing

Microsoft Office C++

Unity JavaScript

HTML/CSS

Interests

■ Travelling ■ Gaming